(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-27T21:11:57.865753",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Thank you all for joining us today for Hakos Baelz's Birthday Live 2026.
Before we begin, I have a few requests and reminders for everyone.
Feel free to enjoy food and drinks in front of your TV, PC, or smartphone, but please be careful not to spill anything on your keyboard.
The official hashtag for this stream is #ReColor3D. Please post about us on social media.
Taking photos with your camera or smartphone during the show is more than welcome. We'd love it if you could share them online to help spread the excitement.
The show will begin shortly, so please stay tuned.
皆様、本日はHakos Baelz生誕祭2026にお越しくださいまして、誠にありがとうございます。
会員に先立ちまして、皆様にお願いとご案内を申し上げます。
テレビやパソコン、スマートフォンの前では、飲食は可能ですが、キーボードにこぼさないようにお気をつけください。
当配信のハッシュタグは#ReColor3Dです。SNSでたくさんポストしてください。
会飲中、カメラやスマートフォンなどによる写真撮影は大歓迎です。たくさんポストして盛り上がっていただけますと幸いです。
それでは開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Thank you all for joining us today for Hakos Baelz's Birthday Live 2026.
Before we begin, I have a few requests and reminders for everyone.
Feel free to enjoy food and drinks in front of your TV, PC, or smartphone, but please be careful not to spill anything on your keyboard.
The official hashtag for this stream is #ReColor3D. Please post about us on social media.
Taking photos with your camera or smartphone during the show is more than welcome. We'd love it if you could share them online to help spread the excitement.
The show will begin shortly, so please stay tuned.
皆様、本日はHakos Baelz生誕祭2026にお越しくださいまして、誠にありがとうございます。
会員に先立ちまして、皆様にお願いとご案内を申し上げます。
テレビやパソコン、スマートフォンの前では、飲食は可能ですが、キーボードにこぼさないようにお気をつけください。
当配信のハッシュタグは#ReColor3Dです。SNSでたくさんポストしてください。
会飲中、カメラやスマートフォンなどによる写真撮影は大歓迎です。たくさんポストして盛り上がっていただけますと幸いです。
それでは開演までしばらくお待ちください。
光の速さで 駆け抜けろ衝動は
The impulse to dash through at the speed of light
何を犠牲にしても 叶えたい強さの覚悟
The resolve for strength to achieve whatever is sacrificed
(No fear) 一度きりの
(No fear) In this one and only
(Trust you) この瞬間に
(Trust you) moment,
賭けてみろ 自分を信じて
risk it all and believe in yourself!
時には運だと言うのなら
If you say that sometimes luck is necessary,
宿命の旋律も 引き寄せてみせよう
I'll draw even fate's melody close.
走れ 今を まだ終われない
Run through the present, I can't let it end yet,
たどり着きたい 場所があるから
because there's a place I want to reach.
その先へと 進め
Move onward beyond that,
涙さえも 強く胸に抱きしめ
holding even your tears tightly against your chest.
そこから始まる ストーリー 果てしなく続く
The story beginning from there continues endlessly,
winning the soul
つかめ 今を変えたいなら 描いた夢を
Seize the present if you want to change it, and the dream you drew...
未来に掲げ 恐れないで
hold high toward the future without fear,
挑め 走れ 今を まだ終われない
challenge it! Run through the present, I can't end yet,
たどり着きたい 場所があるから
because there's a place I want to reach.
その先へと 進め
Move onward beyond that,
涙さえも 強く胸に抱きしめ
holding even your tears tightly against your chest.
そこから始まる ストーリー 果てしなく続く
The story beginning from there continues endlessly,
winning the soul
woh woh woh
うわさ、Everyone!
What's up, everyone!
I am Chaos, the end of ends!
I still race trapped in a cage, I still...
best friend, Bell, take us from Hololive English Promise!
我らはコース、終わりの果て、ざ・えんど
We are Chaos, the end of ends,
氷の二分咲き、黒金の薔薇、何時の日か、ざ・えんど。
blooming in ice, the black-gold rose...
Witness me!
Another year, another not-birthday live!
Thank you so much for coming, everyone!
Did you like the opening act?
The opening show did it!
This year, we have a not-birthday-birthday live again called "RECOLOR 3D".
That is also the hashtag, please use it! RECOLOR 3D.
Um, I don't know, it might be... The theme this year was color for for for many reasons.
Um, I don't know, the theme this year was color for many reasons.
There's also a lot of special things that are happening today, as you may or may not already know.
There's also a lot of special things happening today, as you may or may not already know.
There's a lot of new things being revealed in this live. Maybe a new song? Maybe a new outfit?
I don't know! You're just gonna have to wait and see!
えっと、今年も誕生日じゃない誕生日ライブをやりのたいと思います。みんな来てくれてありがとうございます！
Um, I wanted to do a not-birthday birthday live again this year. Thank you all for coming!
え、今日のライブでね、新しいものがいっぱいあると思いますので、最後まで耳見てくれたら嬉しいです！あ、もう疲れてる、やばい。
And since there'll be lots of new things in today's live, I'd be happy if you tuned in all the way to the end! Ah, I'm already tired, oh no.
はい、あのハッシュタグもぜひぜひあのいっぱいコメントと写真をポストしてください。ありがとうございます！
Yes, please definitely post lots of comments and photos with the hashtag too! Thank you very much!
えっと、um It is my birthday, not birthday, but I'm just so excited to be able to share this day with all of you.
Um, it is my birthday, not birthday, but I'm just so excited to be able to share this day with all of you.
Once I catch my breath, we're going to get this party started. Yeah?
じゃあ、最後まで楽しみにしててください！そこ、次の曲のネツと... I'm going to go to the other stage for the next song so I'll see you guys there, all right?
So please enjoy it all the way to the end! I'm going to go to the other stage for the next song so I'll see you guys there, all right?
I'm going to go now. Um, is that all right? Okay, bye. I'll see you guys there. Race you!
あれが正解なんて
Thinking that's the correct answer...
誰の成れの果て？
Whose tragic end is this?
(なんだったっけのモモモ)
What was it again, mo-mo-mo?
答えも欲しいのもいごって
I want answers, I've wanted it,
これだけ悩んだってしょうがないじゃんね
and worrying this much can't be helped, right?
あれは夢だったって思うことにしたって
Even if I decide to treat it as a dream,
重くしたって
and make it heavy,
でも全部思えないけど
I can't take it all seriously, but
助けてよフォロワー！抗うだけ若さに負け
help me, follower! Struggling just loses to youth,
next, next, lucky, lucky, lucky
ありきたりさ 終わりよ
It's cliché, it's over,
楽なのにとか
even though it should be easy,
ああ もうやだ
ah, I'm already sick of it.
なんて新世界か
What kind of new world is this?
あなた以外は あなた以外は ない ない ない
Nobody else, nobody else, no, no, no!
離れないでよバリア あるはずなの 何か あったならば
Don't leave me, barrier! If there was something there,
happy, jumpin', yeah!
あなたのその手とあたしのこの手を
If your hand and my hand
つないだらもう二度と離さないわ
are linked, I'll never let go again.
あなたのその手があたしのこの手を
If your hand grabs my hand...
掴んだら…以降 お見知り置きを！ my love ♡
once it's grabbed... nice to meet you from now on! my love ♡
これで終わりなんて
Saying this is how it ends,
上がれないままなんて
staying unable to rise up,
どうにかなっちゃって願って願ってね
wishing and hoping somehow, hey,
朝帰りしたりしちゃわんど
don't go coming home at dawn.
なあもう我慢できんペイン！
Hey, I can't take this pain anymore!
pain, pain 痛いってば everyday まゆげをいじれるけど
pain, pain, it hurts everyday, though I can touch my eyebrows,
なんて関係ないな誰よりも猫被りないも結構
that doesn't matter, being unpretentious is fine too.
足は足だ見といてよね
My legs are legs, so watch closely,
目標で終わらせたいなんて
wanting it to end just as a goal,
リスタートできたらって
thinking if I could just restart,
でも無理よもう！
but it's already impossible!
what's on your mind?
ありきたりさ 終わりよ
It's cliché, it's over,
楽なのにとか
even though it should be easy,
ああ もうやだ
ah, I'm already sick of it.
なんて新世界か
What kind of new world is this?
あなた以外は あなた以外は ない ない ない
Nobody else, nobody else, no, no, no!
離れないでよバリア あるはずなの 何か あったならば
Don't leave me, barrier! If there was something there,
happy, jumpin', yeah!
あなたのその手とあたしのこの手を
If your hand and my hand
つないだらもう二度と離さないわ
are linked, I'll never let go again.
あなたのその手があたしのこの手を
If your hand grabs my hand...
掴んだら…以降 お見知り置きを！ my love ♡
once it's grabbed... nice to meet you from now on! my love ♡
お見知り置きを！ my love ♡
Nice to meet you! my love ♡
ラリラリラッタ ラリラ
Lari lari ratta lari ra
CR詠ZY
break away break away cyber level
あの日本一イケいれてる姿仕草お気でしょ
That Japan's #1 coolest look and vibe
Don't you think? Don't you think?
I'm so lazy, たぶんそう
I'm so lazy, probably so
ファイトオンナ並べでるだけのひと
Just a fighting girl lined up
crash crash, pulse vein
Don't you think? Don't you think?
In this world 脳頭には what a beautiful マイジる花びら
In this world, what a beautiful scattering of petals
バラライカ のみたいナ
Wanting a balalaika
ラリラリラッタ ラリラ
Lari lari ratta lari ra
CR詠ZY
一瞬の感情に ride on
Ride on the momentary emotion
心はないない
There is no heart
強気のサムライ
Strong-willed samurai
自我死ね 盛大目でふくらい ready to die!
Die ego, grandly swollen, ready to die!
ほら岩登りあなたの空まく誰の空 あらあらしきひぎちぎて
Look, climbing rocks, your sky, whose sky, tearing rough secrets
ほらその場所で聴こえてくる音の仕掛け
Look, at that place, the trick of the sound you hear
轟くのをのれの調べ 誰かのじゃないのれの調べ
The resounding tune of yourself, not someone else's tune
ラッタララッタラッタ
Ratta la ratta ratta
目の前に広がる世界はブルー ひとまずサムムーブ
The world before me is blue, for now a cold move
peak a boo, peek a tap, there's no need 何そんな張り切ってえらそうに
Peak a boo, peek a tap, no need to look so triumphant
君も愛を
You too, love
右も左も知りもしないで言わないで
Don't speak without knowing right or left
Don't you think? Don't you think?
似たり影が笑う
Similar shadows laugh
世界は見たい
The world wants to see
CR詠ZY
繰り返すように ride on
Ride on like repeating
わかってもいない
Even if you don't understand
あれこれようとらい
Try saying this and that
Tell me something for the new
新しい時代の 期待の時代の
Of the new era, of the expected era,
バイブス
vibes!
Clap back
Move my mind, shooting my side
Save it あなたのその瞬間 Maybe nothing wrong
Save that moment of yours, maybe nothing wrong...
La-Lee-La-Lee-La-La La-Lee-La
誰もがだいた
Everybody embraces it
C-R-A-Z-Y
一瞬の感情に
To instantaneous emotions,
Ride on, ride on, ride on, ride on
心は 95
Heart is ninety-five,
狂気のサムライ
a samurai of madness.
血走りさせた目でゆく Ready to die
With bloodshot eyes, ready to die
ハロー 朝日は昇り あなたの空は 真っ黒な空
Hello, the sun rises, your sky is pitch black
アラアラ ズタズタ引き裂いて
Tearing it apart violently right there
ほらその場所で 聞こえてくるの 話かけ
From that place, a heartbeat begins to echo
驚くのは まだこれから まだこれから
There's still more to come, still more to come
あの街は見て 時計の針 零時の街
Look at that town, clock hands pointing to midnight
たけだけしく いざ Raise your voice
Boldly now, raise your voice
ほらすぐそこで 始まりだすここの宴
Right there, the banquet begins to unfold
奏でるのは 唯一無二のノリの調べ
Playing the one and only unique melody
ビービーブーにしろ注意
Be-be-beware of that beauty
あいつの信者は多い
She's got a lot of fanatics
己を知りなさい bitch
Know yourself, bitch
HDで見えるのに
You can see it all in HD, though
私もあなた様みたいになりたい
I wanna look like you too
教えて教えて 幸せでしょ？
Tell me, tell me, you must be happy, right?
もしこのまま消えたら 愛されるのなら
If I disappear like this and get loved for it,
今すぐにでも綺麗に泣きたい
I'd gladly want to cry beautifully right now
こんなはずじゃないわダヴィンチ
This isn't how it's supposed to be, Da Vinci
もう少しだけベッピンに
Make me a little bit prettier
コントラストも入れてちょうだい
Add some contrast to it too
全世界を殺しめたい
I want to conquer the whole world
Look at this
悲しいかも ayy, ayy, ayy
It's a bit sad, ayy, ayy, ayy
もう少し肌に艶をちょうだい
Give my skin a little more glow
女盛りのめたいやい
Don't underestimate women in their prime
トイレに女神はおったんかい？
Was there a goddess in the toilet?
おったんなら捕まえなさい
If you found her, go catch her
ちゃんみな最近まじかわいい 私を忘れないあの嵐
Chanmina is so cute lately, I won't forget that storm
あのとき私はまだセブンティーン あのとき言ったような
Back then I was still seventeen, you said to me back then
You can't be beautiful, you can't be famous 醜いブスが歌ってんじゃないよ
You can't be beautiful, you can't be famous, an ugly bitch shouldn't be singing
あのとき狂った精神に才能が開花
Back then, my talent blossomed in a deranged mind
味わった幸も不幸も普通じゃなかった
Both happiness and unhappiness were out of the ordinary
本物を君は知っているかい？
Do you know the real thing?
知識と経験のエロス
Eros of knowledge and experience
まだ使い物になってるかい？
Is it still of any use?
女は皆正気じゃない
Women are not all sane
Look at this
悲しいかも ayy, ayy, ayy もう少し肌に艶をちょうだい
It's a bit sad, ayy, ayy, ayy, give my skin a little more glow
女盛りのめたいやい
Don't underestimate women in their prime
トイレに女神はおったんかい？
Was there a goddess in the toilet?
おったんなら捕まえなさい
If you found her, go catch her
Can you hear me mina are you the beauty Say july you are the ma fucking beauty
Can you hear me, mina? Are you the beauty? Say July, you are the ma-fucking beauty
よそ見せず踊りなさい 磨けたらダイヤ美しい
Dance without looking away, polished, a diamond is beautiful
光が敵 いやがって君がいたらダイヤのように美しい
If you're there defying the light, you're as beautiful as a diamond
行きなさい今見せなさい あなたこそダイヤ美しい
Go now and show them, you are the true diamond beauty
I'm a fucking woman and I'm fucking beautiful
God, here I am
We're fucking women and we're fucking beautiful
Look everyone!
I finally have a new outfit!
見て見て見て！ 新衣装どう？ かわいい？ どう？
Look, look, look! How's the new outfit? Cute? How is it?
どう？ ドキドキ？
How? Makes your heart race?
This performance made...
I want to have a close-up! There are so many things I want to show off, starting from the top down!
Look at that hair! Look at that fade! かっこよくない？
Look at that hair! Look at that fade! Isn't it cool?
I asked for a wolf cut.
That's also up, half up, half down, so it's really easy to dance in.
めちゃくちゃ踊りやすくて。可愛いでしょ？まあ、可愛いかっこ、かっこいいっしょ？あはは！
It's so easy to move, and cute, right? Well, cute and cool, cool, right? Haha!
And then,
uh what else?
What else? Oh, my makeup!
Make-upもかわいいしょ！
Makeup's cute too!
And then I have so many like hand accessories as well.
Look at that!
Look how cool that is!
And then we did like a quick scan of the...
T-pose quick scan, quick scan of the body.
Whoa!
There's also something very special.
I have an MC tail now.
If you noticed earlier, normally when I dance,
I have my tail just, you know, free.
But, you know, this is the MC resting tail, because the tail also needs resting periods as well.
So this is my MC tail. Very cute!
I hope you guys like it!
Oh my god!
And this was designed by, of course, the amazing Mika Pikazo!
I designed... めちゃくちゃかわいいデザインになりました！ I designed. Heh heh heh.
I designed... meccha kucha kawaii design ni narimashita! I designed. Heh heh heh.
But, that's not all.
I mean, if I get a new outfit, I feel like it's only fair that
some other people get new outfits! Quick! Quick! Get it, get it, get it!
The backup dancers also get new outfits!
You get an outfit, you get an outfit, everyone gets an outfit. Look at them!
Oh, look, oh shit! Oh yeah, oh wow!
Oh, so sexy! Oh!
So the knee dancers have also upgraded outfits. They have shorts with the boots and the socks and the jacket.
Wow, look at that! Amazing!
And then on the back of the jacket, they have my logo, 一緒にロゴもあります！ Wow, kawaii!
And then on the back of the jacket, they have my logo, isshoni logomo arimasu! Wow, kawaii!
I also designed... not designed, but I wanted the design to be easy for them to dance in as well.
So, this is the upgraded baedance team!
Yay! どう、かわいい！
Yay! Do, kawaii!
あん… ポーズ！ ポーズ！ かわいい！ Yay!
An... pose! Pose! Kawaii! Yay!
Well, since we all have new outfits, I think it's only fitting that we continue the rest of the live
like this, with our new outfits!
じゃ、踊りますか！
Ja, odorimashu ka!
We're gonna do the next song on that stage over there.
Let's go!
おいしょ、おいしょ、緊張すんな、はい、じゃ、どうぞ！
Oishot, oishot, kinchou suruna, hai, ja, dōzo!
正体あらわせ (Raon！)
Show your true form (Raon!)
正体あらわせ
Show your true form
月の光を飲む ぼくの夜が来た
Drinking the moonlight, my night has come
けたたましく現れる one two
Appearing clamorously, one, two
危険を探して knock, knock, knock！
Searching for danger, knock, knock, knock!
don't mess it up！
Don't mess it up!
forget it, make a finger
窓を見て you can see my eyes
Look at the window, you can see my eyes
その瞳に出会ったら お前は仲間だ カム カム say it！
Meet my gaze, and you're my ally, come, come, say it!
けしからぬものか ましおなものか (tick-tock-tock)
Are you scandalous, or are you innocent? (Tick-tock-tock)
正体あらわせ ay ta da da da da (ho！)
Show your true form, ay ta da da da da (Ho!)
変装して love it ぼく見れて know it らいらい らいら いや (come again？)
Disguise and love it, see me and know it, rairai raira iya (Come again?)
明かせ love it 存在 know it ないないないないばい (show me show me eyes)
Reveal and love it, exist and know it, nainainainai-bye (Show me, show me eyes)
don't worry 傷つけないよ
Don't worry, I won't hurt you
ライライライヤ (ライライライヤ)
Rairairaiya (Rairairaiya)
i let you このミステリーに あい や い や い や い や い や -
I let you, into this mystery, ai ya ya ya ya ya ya -
see this finger trap！
See this finger trap!
明日は make it rough 今日は make it fire
Tomorrow make it rough, today make it fire
目を避けないで make it loud your voice
Don't look away, make it loud your voice
よしよし 止め 恐れ お狐様に任せよ (ha！)
There, there, stop the fear, leave it to the fox queen! (Ha!)
光を騙して作るんだ night
Tricking the light to create the night
あちこち目覚めて 闇が喝采
Awakening everywhere, darkness cheers
ねえ ほら こっち おいで
Hey, come over here
yeah！ just shout out the spell！
Yeah! Just shout out the spell!
けしからぬものか ましおなものか (tick-tock-tick-tock)
Are you scandalous, or are you innocent? (Tick-tock-tick-tock)
正体あらわせ ay ta da da da da (ho！)
Show your true form, ay ta da da da da (Ho!)
未体験 love it ぼく は know it
Unexperienced love it, I know it
らいらい らいら いや (come again？)
Rairai raira iya (Come again?)
この世界 変える see me 期待して (show me show me eyes)
Change this world, see me, anticipate it (Show me, show me eyes)
don't worry 傷つけないよ
Don't worry, I won't hurt you
ライライライヤ (ライライライヤ)
Rairairaiya (Rairairaiya)
i let you さあ 魅惑魔魅に あい や い や い や い や い や -
I let you, now into fascination, ai ya ya ya ya ya ya -
hey！ follow the queen fox i'm the real master of this night
Hey! Follow the queen fox, I'm the real master of this night
hey！ follow your queen fox ミセラナレタ
Hey! Follow your queen fox, captivated
肩並べた ぼくたちのshow window
Standing shoulder to shoulder, our show window
見透かす この眼差し 君に届いている？
Seeing right through, is this gaze reaching you?
why don't you know？ it's time now どんな 姿 でも 構わ ない 世界 へ
Why don't you know? It's time now, to a world where any form is fine
けしからぬものか ましおなものか 正体あらわせ 正体あらわせ
Are you scandalous, or are you innocent? Show your true form, show your true form
変装して love it ぼく見れて know it らいらい らいら いや (come again？)
Disguise and love it, see me and know it, rairai raira iya (Come again?)
明かせ love it 存在 know it
Reveal and love it, exist and know it
時には噛んだりして
Bite down from time to time,
痛みを覚えさせて
and let me remember what pain feels like.
溢れるエキタイで汚してよ 全部
Stain my entirety with that overflowing fluid, all of it.
足の先からずっと 躰わせたその神経はもう
From the tips of my toes, that nerve that's been driven wild—
感覚に溺れる 身体ココロを連れて
drowning in sensation, taking body and heart along.
指くわえた我慢の中 欲しえんのが理想?
With a finger in my mouth holding back, is what is desired an ideal?
いらない 全てはいらない
I don't need it, don't need any of it.
磨き上げている邪魔なPRIDE
A shined-up, obtrusive PRIDE.
無意味な世界のルールくらい 無駄としか言い様がない
The rules of this meaningless world are nothing short of pointless.
隠しているあなたのSTYLE
Your STYLE that you've kept hidden away—
剥き出しにあるがままDIVE
dive right in, completely bare and as you are.
そこに生まれるのは期待 外れなんかじゃない 頂上のSMILE
What's born there is expectation, not a disappointment at all—a smile at the peak.
Finger-spinning trap
Just shout out the spell!
Fall on Queen Fox!
威風堂々
Majestic and proud,
存分に味わったりして
Savoring it to your heart's content,
痛みを思い出させて
make me remember the pain.
溢れる期待で汚してよ全部
Stain me completely with overflowing expectations.
足の先からずっと 交わしたその神経はもう
From the tips of my toes, the nerves we shared—
感触に溺れる身体
drowning in sensation, body and soul
心を連れて
taking my heart along with it.
指くわえた我慢の中
With a finger in my mouth holding back,
逃げ出したいがままの心をつれて
taking my heart that just wants to run away.
いらない 全てはいらない
I don't need it, don't need any of it.
磨き上げてる邪魔な
A shined-up, obtrusive...
無意味な世界のルールくらい無駄としか言いようがない
The rules of this meaningless world are nothing short of pointless.
タイムリミットが来ようが内幕隠しているあなたのスタイル
Whatever the time limit, hiding your inner style—
剥き出しにあるがままそこに出るのも期待外れなんかじゃない
coming out completely bare and as you are is no disappointment at all.
叩きのめすまいる 吐き寄せた相性
A beating smile, the affinity we drew together,
耳に吹きかける感情 破裂しそうな胸騒ぎだす細胞
emotions whispered in your ear, cells with a heart-pounding panic.
ぬぎかけてるシャツ優しく裂いてよ
Kindly rip open the shirt I'm taking off,
まずかまわずget 自由な世界のど真ん中
no worries, get flying right in the middle of a free world.
吐き寄せた相性 耳に吹きかける感情
The affinity we drew together, emotions whispered in your ear,
張り裂そうな胸騒ぎだす細胞 抜け出してるシャツ
cells with a heart-pounding panic, the shirt slipping off—
優しく裂いてよ まあ かまわず get fly まぁ 黙らせないで
kindly rip it open, no worries, get fly, well, don't silence me!
自由な世界の一番中
Right in the center of a free world,
夢見ての過剰証
an excessive proof of dreaming.
いらない 全てはいらない
I don't need it, don't need any of it.
おじけづいた野望のトライ マジックなんてそこにない
A hesitant ambition's try, there's no magic there.
目に見える憐れな未来 思い通りにできるライフ
A visible pathetic future, a life you can make as you please.
手にできるかはあなた次第 隠したりなんかはしない
Whether you can hold it is up to you, I won't hide anything.
誰よりも誇らしくできるまい ほらこの世界の中
Proudly more than anyone, look, in this world—
他にはない確かなもの 自分以外は皆無し
there's nothing certain besides yourself, everyone else is none.
小さくなってる場合じゃない いつだってNo Time!
This is no time to be shrinking away, it's always No Time!
上限値越え エンジン全開でいっちゃえ burn burn burn
Cross your upper limits, full throttle and go burn burn burn!
突き抜けてバイバイじゃん？ だってノータイム
Punching through with a bye-bye right? Because there's no time!
オールライト 飛び込んでこえんじん 全開で一緒に burn burn burn
All right, dive in, engine full throttle together, burn burn burn!
ぶちまけてるのは素気持ちいいのもう あるがままの思いで
What we're spilling out is raw pleasure, with emotions just as they are.
ジャッチーなりでゲットだぜ!
Judiciously get it!
いらない 全てはいらない
I don't need it, don't need any of it.
おじけづいた野望のトライ マジックなんてそこにない
A hesitant ambition's try, there's no magic there.
目に見える憐れな未来 思い通りにできるライフ
A visible pathetic future, a life you can make as you please.
手にできるかはあなた次第 隠したりなんかはしない
Whether you can hold it is up to you, I won't hide anything.
誰よりも誇らしくできるまい ほらこの世界の中
Proudly more than anyone, look, in this world—
他にはない確かなもの 自分以外は皆無し
there's nothing certain besides yourself, everyone else is none.
小さくなってる場合じゃない いつだってNo Time!
This is no time to be shrinking away, it's always No Time!
貫いて するどきラつかせて 希望 もっと本気出していいよ
Piercing through, letting your sharp hopes glint, you can get more serious!
Hit me up!
Come chase me!
Everyday I spent crying 'bout almost-loves turned complicated
On the way yah, my heart got torn up, shredded, all but dead and
Now they say I, I'm just a masochist, they're sick of it
Boy take a hint, you ain't gon' ever get this
Pedal to the metal, shooting straight to the stars
Got a cravin', like the danger on me
(Yeah she like it like that, like that)
Up another level, temptation you just can't deny
Come get a taste but can't say I won't bite
(So hit me up!)
(Heading out...)
ow!
huh
come chase me
everyday i
spent crying 'bout almost-loves turned complicated
Everyday I spent crying
'bout almost-loves turned complicated,
on the way yah
on the way, yeah.
my heart got torn up,
shredded, all but dead and
My heart got torn up,
shredded, all but dead,
now they say i
i'm just a masochist, they're sick of it
and now they say I'm just
a masochist, they're sick of it.
boy take a hint
you ain't gon' ever get this
pedal to the metal shootin' straight to the stars
Pedal to the metal,
shootin' straight to the stars,
got a cavin', like the danger on me
got a craving, like the danger on me.
(yeah she like it like that, like that)
up another level
temptation you just can't deny
come get a taste but can't say i won't bite
supersonic, i'm heading out, i'm gonna (ahh)
Supersonic, I'm heading out, I'm gonna— (Ah!)
in my eyes, nirvana (oh i'm taking off now!)
pushing for the high, my lover, i gotta (run)
Pushing for the high, my lover, I gotta— (Run!)
but it's fun to see you try
(so hit me up!)
off the map i'mma take it, all my energy
(So hit me up!) Off the map,
I'mma take it, all my energy!
(so hit me up!)
speedin' up fast
ready, target locked
(So hit me up!) Speedin' up fast,
ready, target locked!
(so hit me up!)
hit the dash, i'm upgraded and you want a piece
(So hit me up!) Hit the dash,
I'm upgraded and you want a piece!
(so hit me up!)
so hit me up, ah
(So hit me up!) So hit me up, ah!
i never stop
in in territory
In a new territory,
i'm on the edge of glory
(boy just watch how i move)
give me that rush
Gimme that rush,
got no regrets in my mind
boy's on you this time
Boy, it's on you this time,
so hit me up out of luck volume up
so hit me up, outta luck, volume up!
you got a crush?
such a cliche your bad boy charms
thought i'd fall right back in your arms
Such a cliché, your bad boy charms,
thought I'd fall right back in your arms.
wasn't enough you needed more
now you're begging to let you score
surely you'll take it all in stride
i'mma be busy tonight
goodbye goodbye
gotta leave you dry
always try'na play it cool
20/20 vision on me
just outside my field of view
(yeah she like it like that, like that)
engine booming, that's my cue
catch me if you can, you better
keep up the chase, boy you're falling behind
supersonic, i'm heading out, i'm gonna (ahh)
Supersonic, I'm heading out, I'm gonna— (Ah!)
in my eyes, nirvana (oh i'm taking off now!)
pushing for the high, my lover, i gotta (run)
Pushing for the high, my lover, I gotta— (Run!)
but it's fun to see you try
(so hit me up!)
off the map i'mma take it, all my energy
(So hit me up!) Off the map,
I'mma take it, all my energy!
(so hit me up!)
speedin' up fast
ready, target locked
(So hit me up!) Speedin' up fast,
ready, target locked!
(so hit me up!)
hit the dash, i'm upgraded and you want a piece
(So hit me up!) Hit the dash,
I''m upgraded and you want a piece!
(so hit me up!)
so hit me up, ah
(So hit me up!) So hit me up, ah!
i never stop
in a new territory
i'm on the edge of glory
(boy just watch how i move)
gimme that rush
got no regrets in my mind
boy's on you this time
Boy, it's on you this time,
so hit me up outta luck volume up
you got a crush?
(ahh)
just barely wasn't enough
(Ah!) Just barely wasn't enough,
you shoulda
(ahh)
given me all that you got
you shoulda— (Ah!) given me
all that you got,
you coulda
coming full circle
you coulda! Coming full circle,
i hit a nerve, oh!
top spot, getting hot
watch me run it up
(so hit me up!)
rev it up and make that
vroom vroom vroom vroom
(So hit me up!) Rev it up and make that
vroom, vroom, vroom, vroom!
(hit me up!)
when i hit you with that
zoom zoom zoom zoom
(Hit me up!) When I hit you with that
zoom, zoom, zoom, zoom!
(hit me up!)
if you know what's good for
you ooh ooh ooh
feel me?
(Hit me up!) If you know what's good for
you, ooh, ooh, ooh... Feel me?
now i'm back in charge
rise out of the dark
Yeah!
How did you enjoy, Dad?
Did you guys enjoy?
We had a couple of songs
with a couple of important people
which I want to call in to help with this next MC part.
which I want to call in to help
with this next MC part.
Special guests! Special guests!
Hey hey hey! Let's welcome IRyS and Calli!
Hey, hey, hey! Let's welcome
IRyS and Calli!
Why don't you introduce yourself please? Please go ahead.
Why don't you introduce yourselves, please?
Please, go ahead.
HoloLive English ChadCast, no Mori Calliope des! What's up?
Hololive English ChadCast,
Mori Calliope desu! What's up?
Hope you enjoyed our performances! Yeah!
Hope you enjoyed our performances!
Yeah!
Hi Riscuits! IRyS also from Chadcast!
Hi Riscuits! IRyS also
from Chadcast!
Let's go! Dad, did you hear a rumble?
Let's go! Dad, did you
hear a rumble?
Yeah! What's this movement?
Did you say your name? Rumble?
I said rumble.
Oh! I'm pretty sure she said IRyS. My brain's not working. It's a big day, guys.
Oh! I'm pretty sure she said IRyS.
My brain's not working, it's a big day!
Cuz she's dancing. Yeah, it's a big... Guys!
Cuz she's dancing! Yeah, it's a big—
Guys!
Yeah. Oh, yeah! I mean, yeah, obviously. Yeah, woo!
Yeah. Oh, yeah, I mean,
yeah, obviously, yeah, woo!
What did you think? It's so cool! You look like a K-pop star.
What did you think? It's so cool!
You look like a K-pop star.
Oh, yeah! I'm so glad you like it. And look, the MC tail is back, you know.
Oh, yeah, I'm so glad you like it.
And look, the MC tail is back, you know.
I've got to put it to rest for a little bit, you know, after all that dancing. So special.
I've got to put it to rest for a little bit,
you know, after all that dancing. So special.
Yeah! Don't touch it. Don't touch it. We performed some songs together.
Yeah! Don't touch it, don't touch it.
We performed some songs together.
Um, first we had... If you... No, well, I guess it's on brand!
Um, first we had... If you... no,
well, I guess it's on brand, yes!
Yeah, we know! Yeah, we know. It's awesome. It's great.
Yeah, we know! Yeah, we know.
It's awesome, it's great.
It was a sexy song! How do you feel about that song?
It was a sexy song!
How do you feel about that song?
Thank you so much. How do you feel? Yeah. How do you feel about that song?
Thank you so much. How do you feel?
Yeah. How do you feel about that song?
Feelings? Thoughts? I feel great about it.
Feelings? Thoughts?
I feel great about it!
I think it was an amazing interview... Which guy is this? Hit! So, hit me up! Hit me up!
I think it was an amazing interview.
Which guy is this? Hit! So, hit me up!
ね
ne
Dancing start!
Dancing starts!
Did you guys know it's my birthday?
Not birthday...
Birthday, but not birthday.
Unbirthday.
She's being unbirthdayed.
But...
That sounds so wrong.
Save it for the chatcast.
I reserve the chatcast.
But after dancing, I am feeling a little bit, you know...
Hot?
Hot!
It's getting hot in here.
Is she going to take off all her clothes?
IRyS, you're strengthened.
Maybe not clothes.
What is she taking off?
She's going to take off her pants!
Why would she take off her pants, IRyS?
What is she thinking about?
All right, you know what?
Okay, wait, no.
Sae, you need to be stopped.
Ah, a, kuzo!
Oh, she's coming in.
Behold!
I took off my jacket!
Oh, my god, she looks so fancy here!
You can see all my, all my, all my accessories now.
Kakkoi!
Fuketto!
I love the spike band!
Yeah!
These aren't solos on the floor, but I have like arm cuffs now as well.
Kakkoi!
Now I can dance even more without restrictions!
She's even more dynamic!
No more tails to get in the way either, like...
Oh, my god, they're popping off.
All the arms.
Masaka nanode ne!
Since we're all here together...
How would you guys feel about maybe doing one more song together?
Okay!
I don't have the energy, but I'll do my best!
Ganbare! Ganbare! Ganbare! Ganbare!
You can do it!
That being said, I hope you guys are ready as well.
We're going to bring you one more chatcast performance!
Let's go!
Ready? Senno!
あじまう　あじまう　あじまーう！
Ajimau, ajimau, ajimaū!
宿題がぜっっぜん終わらない、全国のヤバめな諸君！
Shukudai ga sezen owaranai zankoku no yabamena shokun!
時間がなければ、眠らなきゃいいじゃない
Jikan ga nakereba nemuranakya ii ja nai!
がんばれ、がんばれ、あたし…
Ganbare, ganbare, atashi...
パーリラ脳内フロア
Paralyzed nōnai furōni
暴れてるカルバブル
Abureteru karubaburu
アドレナリンダブダブ
Adorenarin dabudabu
究極のPANIGHT
Kyokugen no PANIGHT
パリナイ！パリナイ！パーラパッパパリナイ！
Parinai! Parinai! Pārapappa parinai!
パリナイ！パリナイ！おわるくない？
Parinai! Parinai! Owaranai nai?
we are ＼NEGI☆U／
We are
EGI☆U/
we are ＼NEGI☆U／
We are
EGI☆U/
we are ＼NEGI☆U／
We are
EGI☆U/
let's go！！
Let's go!!
スゴイ ヤバイ パナイ 物足りない ないない尽くしで止めとない
Sugoi yabai panai mono tarinai nai nai tsukushi de tome tonai
スゴイ ヤバイ パナイ saturday night とにかくもうやるしかないどすこい
Sugoi yabai panai saturday night tonikaku mou yaru shika nai dosu koi
ヤバイ パナイ 物足りない 全力モノモノ申したいよ
Yabai panai mono tarinai zenryoku monosomo nosho shitai yo
たった一度の青春は 毎日enjoy party night
Tatta ichido no seishun wa mainichi enjoy party night
あーお喋りの旦那様…
Ā okumari no dannasama...
え、そうじゃない様！
E, sō ja nai sama!
ご唱和ください！
Goshōwa kudasai!
それゆけ say
Sore yuke say
wow＼wow／×3
Wow \wow/ ×3
ddd dj！！
D D D DJ!!
pa pa pa pa... panight！！
Pa pa pa pa... panight!!
うえーーーのーーーん うん
Uehhhhh ung...
ぷっぷぷうーーん everyday sing along
Pupuquāg! Everyday sing along!
でっち上げ進化論 陽キャでも陰キャでも勉強だ wassup！！ wassup！！
Decchi age shinkaron yōkya demo inkyamo benkyō da wassup!! wassup!!
太陽は銀河系！？ おしゃべりノンノンノン！
Taiyō wa gingakei!? Oshare non non non!
遊びじゃダメダメ ごめんなさい！
Asobi ja dame dame gomen nasai!
朝が来て眠れないどうしよう…
Asa ga kite nemurenai dōshiyō...
神様も両手上げてfly high なんとかするしかない
Kamisama mo ryōte agete fly high nantoka suru shika nai
頑張れるってド派手にかましちやる ネバギバput your hands up
Ganbare dekiru tte dokuhate ni kamashicharu neba gi ba put your hands up!
タリライ！タリライ！タラッタッタタリライ！
Tarirai! Tarirai! Tarattatta tarirai!
タリライ！タリライ！時間がない
Tarirai! Tarirai! Jikan ga nai
we are ＼NEGI☆U／
We are
EGI☆U/
we are ＼NEGI☆U／
We are
EGI☆U/
we are ＼NEGI☆U／
We are
EGI☆U/
let's go！！
Let's go!!
あ、えと、れっつごー↑w
A, eto, re-tSU-GŌ! w
スゴイ ヤバイ パナイ 物足りない 代打のバッターかたじけない
Sugoi yabai panai mono tarinai daidai no batter ka tajikei nai
スゴイ ヤバイ パナイ sunday night とにかくもうやるしかないどすこい
Sugoi yabai panai sunday night tonikaku mou yaru shika nai dosu koi
ヤバイ パナイ 物足りない 宿題やっぱり終わらない
Yabai panai mono tarinai shukudai yappari owaranai
たった一度の青春は 脳内happy！party night
Tatta ichido no seishun wa nōnai happy! party night
ねえちぃ〜、あてっち〜、おわにんですよおれ〜
Neechii~ Atetchi~ Owanyondesuyoore~
スバル先輩〜！！この問題全然わかんないんですけど〜！！
Subaru-senpai~!! Kono mondai zenzen wakannain desukedo~!!
えっっ！何その鉛筆？！めちゃ可愛いじゃん、いいなー！！
Ew! Nan sono enpitsu?! Meccha kawaii jan, ii nā~!!
でしょう〜 wwキラキラ光るんです よ〜ほほほ
Deshō~ ww Kirakira hikarundesu yo~ hohōho!
え、へ、へ、みんな、げんきだ なあ…
E, he, he, minna, genki da nā...
よ、陽キャって、こんな時 も、すごい なあ…
Yo, yōkya tte, konna toki mo, sugoi nā...
は は は は…… えと ‥ はは… ぱ 、ぱーりー ↗w
Ha ha ha ha...... e to... haha... pa-, pāryō! ↑w
朝が来て眠れないどうしよう…
Asa ga kite nemurenai dōshiyō...
神様も両手上げてfly high
Kamisama mo ryōte agete fly high
なんとかするしかない 頑張れるって
Nantoka suru shika nai ganbare dekiru tte
ド派手にかましちやるネバギバput your hands up
Dohade ni kamashicharu neba gi ba put your hands up!
タリライ！タリライ！タラッタッタタリライ！
Tarirai! Tarirai! Tarattatta tarirai!
タリライ！タリライ！時間がない
Tarirai! Tarirai! Jikan ga nai
we are ＼NEGI☆U／
We are
EGI☆U/
we are ＼NEGI☆U／
We are
EGI☆U/
we are ＼NEGI☆U／
We are
EGI☆U/
let's go！！
Let's go!!
スゴイ ヤバイ パナイ 物足りない ないない尽くしで止めとない
Sugoi yabai panai mono tarinai nai nai tsukushi de tome tonai
スゴイ ヤバイ パナイ saturday night とにかくもうやるしかないどすこい
Sugoi yabai panai saturday night tonikaku mou yaru shika nai dosu koi
ヤバイ パナイ 物足りない 大体のパッサカタチけない
Yabai panai mono tarinai taitai no passa katachikenai
スゴイ ヤバイ パナイ sunday night とにかくもうやるしかないどすこい
Sugoi yabai panai sunday night tonikaku mou yaru shika nai dosu koi
ヤバイ パナイ 物足りない 宿題やっぱり終わらない
Yabai panai mono tarinai shukudai yappari owaranai
たった一度の青春は のないhappy！party night
Tatta ichido no seishun wa nonai happy! party night
アイリスがりい！終わんないんです！
Iroisu-garii! Owanaindesu!
この問題全然わかんないんですけど！
Kono mondai zenzen wakannain desu kedo!
でしょう！キラキラ光るんですよう！
Deshō! Kirakira hikarundesuyo!
もりがりい！みんな元気だな！
Mori-garii! Minna genki dana!
ふきょをきゃってこんなときもすごいな！
Fukyo o kyatte konnatoki mo sugoina!
party party! Woo!
お描きになった そんな音楽 現在使われておりません
The music you've drawn is no longer in use.
もう一度お描きなおしてください 意味わかんねぇ
Please redraw it once more. Makes no sense!
意味わかんねぇ
Makes no sense!
どうせ誰も聴いてなんかないさ
Nobody's listening anyway, right?
音楽なんて全部ファッション
Music is all just fashion.
音楽なんて選手退場案内
Music is a player dismissal notice.
どうせ何も伝えたくないじゃないさ
You don't want to convey anything anyway, right?
なんとなくドクドクプライド 愛なんてとびきりサイテーでいい
Just thumping pride. Love can be exceptionally awful.
どうしたってどう見たってそうしたってでも大渋滞
No matter what, however you look at it, it's a massive traffic jam.
どいつもこいつもそいつもあいつもちぐはぐで満身創痍とエルスターも欲しがる
Everyone, mismatched and battered, and even Elstar wants it.
パンチライン欲しいの 意味とかどっちだっていいよ
I want a punchline. Meaning or whatever doesn't matter.
歌詞とかどうでもいいので乗れるのください
Lyrics or whatever are fine, so give me something I can ride to!
さあみんなで笑いましょう
Come on, let's all laugh together.
芸術よりすの代償
The price of being raw rather than art.
バイラスにひどい代償 じゃあどうすの
A terrible price for a virus. Then what will you do?
それでいいんだっけ 朝まで回り続けて
Is that fine? Keep spinning until morning.
ふざけるな バイバイ バズメロディ 疑えよ大体 嘘ばかり
Don't mess around, bye-bye buzz melody. Doubt it, mostly lies!
負け犬が逆説でも理想でもいい
Even as a loser, paradox or ideal is fine.
君の歌かかったもうはどうしたんだい
Your song started playing, what happened?
ざまでもオーマイ嘘じゃない
Even so, oh my, it's not a lie.
お金や理性で満たす前に
Before filling up with money or reason,
負け犬が覚醒せよ子供たちよ
Losers, wake up, children!
君の歌かかったもうはどうしたんだい
Your song started playing, what happened?
お描きになった そんな音楽 現在使われておりません
The music you've drawn is no longer in use.
ポップソングヒットソング聴いてもう一度お描きなおしてください
Please listen to pop and hit songs and redraw it once more.
ああもうハイからサッカバッカシャラクサイわ
Ah, high-collared, stuck-up, and cheeky!
こいつもちいつもそいつもちいつもうんざり
Everyone, this guy, that guy, I'm sick of it all.
君は誰？どうしたってどう見たってそうしたってでも大渋滞
Who are you? No matter what, however you look at it, a massive traffic jam.
どれでもあっちこっちそっちどっち満身創痍とエリスだかも欲しがる
Everywhere, here, there, which way, battered and Elstar wants it too.
パンチライン欲しいの 意味とかどっちだっていいよ
I want a punchline. Meaning or whatever doesn't matter.
歌詞とかどうでもいいので伸びるのください
Lyrics don't matter, just give me something that goes viral.
さあみんなで払いましょう
Come on, let's laugh it off together.
芸術よりすの代償
The price of being raw rather than art.
バイラスにひどい代償 じゃあどうすの
A terrible price for a virus. Then what will you do?
それでいいんだって
Is that fine?
頭空回り死んでいく
Head spinning in circles, dying away.
ふざけるなバイバイバズメロディ
Don't mess around, bye-bye buzz melody.
疑えよタイガイ嘘ばかり
Doubt it, mostly lies!
負け犬が逆説でも理想でもいい 君の歌かかったもうはどうしたんだい
Even as a loser, paradox or ideal is fine. Your song started playing, what happened?
このままだとだって終われない 欲しいのはきっと金じゃない
This way, we can't end. What we want surely isn't money.
変な覚醒せよ子供たちよ
Strange awakening, wake up, children!
君の歌かったもんはどこ行ったんだ ふざけるな
Where did your song go? Don't mess around!
ふざけるなバイバイバズメロディ 歌えよタイガイ嘘ばかり
Don't mess around, bye-bye buzz melody. Sing along, mostly lies!
負け犬が逆説でも理想でもいい 君の歌かかったもうはどうしたんだい
Even as a loser, paradox or ideal is fine. Your song started playing, what happened?
さまでもオーマイ嘘じゃない お金や理性で満たす前に
Even so, oh my, it's not a lie. Before filling up with money or reason,
負け犬が覚醒せよ子供たちよ
Losers, wake up, children!
僕の歌かかったもうはどうしたんだい
My song started playing, what happened?
意味わかんねぇ 意味わかんねぇよ！
Makes no sense, makes no sense at all!
意味わかんねぇ
Makes no sense!
まちゃる Bla-bla-bla-bla-bla
Machare V, blah, blah, blah, blah,
I'm a V!
まちゃる Bla-bla-bla-bla-bla
Machare V, blah, blah, blah, blah,
I'm a V!
まちゃる Bla-bla-bla-bla-bla I'm a V!
Machare V, blah, blah, blah, blah, I'm a V!
だじゃれ Bla-bla-bla-bla-bla I'm a V!
Daravita, daravita, rauka, blah, blah, blah!
高々生々名も無き混沌 さわらば可愛いね混沌 高鳴か遥かほら
So high, so raw, nameless chaos. Farewell, cute chaos. Thumping far away, look!
落としてあげる
I'll drop you down.
はい尊い、はいゅら、でも目がキュートなら免罪符、とか腹立てられてる、いってるメンタルは
Yes, precious, yes yura, but if your eyes are cute, it's a get-out-of-jail card, or getting pissed off, the mental state saying—
最高 Smile で ごまかしてがファントム
Ah, psychos, smile there. Conceal it like a phantom.
ごまかしたんでしょ 初心証にさばさばたばば
You concealed it, didn't you? Served right to your maiden heart, bam bam.
I am a V!
I'm a V! I'm a V! I'm a V! I'm a V!
I am a V! だなてぃ！ ばみたに たらわやよ
I am a V! Danati! Bamidala, wayayoyo!
夢見てる少年よ 夢見てる少女で
Dreaming boy, dreaming girl,
VならVだわ 甘い甘い甘い甘いノウ チョン切りがりがもそう
If V, it's V, sweet, sweet, sweet, sweet now, cutting off is also so.
Whatever せの！ われがセンター 誰よりも客寄せのパンダ Whatever なんだ まるで生んだ ちかあいせょしょせん
Whatever senow, who's the center, a panda drawing customers more than anyone, whatever nanda, as if born, close love...
M-I-V M-I-C 荒いざらい 甘い汁 皿に乾杯
M-I-V, M-I-C, stripped bare, sweet nectar, cheers on a plate!
woke up today feelin’ less than great
Woke up today, feelin' less than great,
got my work done late oh (screw these deadlines)
(seriously) missed the train, two hour wait and i barely ate
(Seriously) missed the train, two-hour wait and I barely ate,
just what is my life
seems like everybody’s got it all figured out
Seems like everybody's got it all figured out.
no matter where the hell i go i always end up getting lost somehow
despite guiding my way it’s slowly fizzing out
Despite guiding my way, it's slowly fizzing out.
every night in my bed i look up to the stars
‘cause i know what it’s like to be so close and yet so far, oh
'Cause I know what it's like to be so close and yet so far, oh.
all these thoughts in my head and i fight the mental war
‘cause i really need to know, i need to know, i need you now, i need you
'Cause I really need to know, I need to know, I need you now, I need you.
i’ma need you to understand that
I'ma need you to understand that
i can be a handful, hard to handle, down in flames, everything i touch
I can be a handful, hard to handle, down in flames, everything I touch—
is it a scandal if you try and screw it up sometimes
i don’t need your guidance or advice, i know i’m right where i want to be
I don't need your guidance or advice, I know I'm right where I want to be,
my way
and all the people say
i’m a mess, i’m a mess, i’m a mess (ah)
"I'm a mess, I'm a mess, I'm a mess!" (Ah)
i’m a mess, so what a mess, that’s what i like about me best (bae)
I'm a mess, so what a mess, that's what I like about me best! (Bae)
why don’t we throw the dice, let’s see what kind of trouble we can get into tonight (uh huh)
Why don't we throw the dice, let's see what kind of trouble we can get into tonight? (Uh-huh)
i like a little chaos in my life that’s right (yep)
I like a little chaos in my life, that's right. (Yep)
what’s with all the sugar, let me add a little spice, yeah
What's with all the sugar? Let me add a little spice, yeah.
seems like everybody’s got it all figured out
Seems like everybody's got it all figured out,
well ain’t that good for them ‘cause so have i by now
Well, ain't that good for them 'cause so have I by now?
it’s my journey to take and i will find my route
It's my journey to take and I will find my route.
when i go to bed and i look up at the stars
i feel a sense of calm in knowing that there’s something much greater than us
I feel a sense of calm in knowing that there's something much greater than us.
and don’t you think the point of life is having fun (huh)
And don't you think the point of life is having fun? (Huh)
‘cause i really need to know, i need to know, i need you now, i need you
'Cause I really need to know, I need to know, I need you now, I need you.
i’ma need you to understand that
I'ma need you to understand that
i can be a handful, hard to handle, down in flames, everything i touch
I can be a handful, hard to handle, down in flames, everything I touch—
is it a scandal if you try, no no no no
i realize that all i needed has been right here by my side
all this time (come on, come on)
all this time
hey
i can be a handful, hard to handle, down in flames, everything i touch
I can be a handful, hard to handle, down in flames, everything I touch—
is it a scandal if you try and screw it up sometimes
i don’t need your guidance or advice, i know i’m right where i want to be
I don't need your guidance or advice, I know I'm right where I want to be,
my way
too bad you thought you got me chained ( too bad )
Too bad you thought you got me chained (too bad)!
now i’m flying, can’t be tamed ( nah )
Now I'm flying, can't be tamed (nah)!
let the wind carry away my thoughts and i know now i’m free
Let the wind carry away my thoughts and I know now I'm free!
and you doubted that i would, now i showed you that i could
Ah!
God!
I'm so tired!
I hope you guys have been enjoying the show!
We had so many bangers after bangers after bangers, a lot of dancing!
We had PARADE, we had Cyberpunk, Dead Boy, we had V!
My arms are dead, everything's dead.
But that's not the end of the show yet!
We got to keep going on and on and on and on and on!
And here I bring you a very, very, very important and uh exciting announcement.
Um, I am about to perform a song that no one has heard before.
No one, except for me!
Because it's my new song!
Um, I've been hyping this up for a while now, because I'm really, really excited.
And this will be the first time that I'm sharing it with all of you.
So I hope you enjoy! More information after my performance, 'cause you got to see it first, you know?
Wish me luck. Um, I'm nervous.
But we got this! Kore kara wa shin kyoku desu!
Man, I'm so nervous right now, but I'll do my best with the performance! Here it goes!
준비
Junbi!
that 's good game , what a shame
That's good game, what a shame,
players , they all complain
Players, they all complain:
\" why me ? \" , \" no , not again \"
"Why me?", "No, not again!"
shout \" ra - ta - ta , \" but
Shout "Ra-ta-ta," but—
ain't got time , so dry those eyes
Ain't got time, so dry those eyes,
look around , what 's that i spy ?
Look around, what's that I spy?
the broken and bruised
i 'll got something to prove now
I've got something to prove now!
abracadabra , let 's go
Abracadabra, let's go,
watch them like dust as they fall ( they fall )
Watch them like dust as they fall!
끝까지 가보자 go
Kkeunkkaji gaboja go,
나는 내 맘대로 해
Naneun nae mamdaero hae!
double one , double win
Double one, double win,
lowly to lottery
do or die
we hit that high
( snake eyes , snake eyes )
(Snake eyes, snake eyes!)
come on , don\u2019t be shy
Come on, don't be shy!
( snake eyes , snake eyes )
(Snake eyes, snake eyes!)
뜨겁게 따라 올라 (불타올라)
Tteogeopge ttara olla (bultaolla)!
놀아 all day , all night
Nora all day, all night!
so turn it up , can\u2019t stop , won\u2019t stop preachin
So turn it up, can't stop, won't stop preachin',
who said the sky \u2019s a limit show th \u0435m that we mean business
Who said the sky's a limit? Show them that we mean business,
w\u0435 are the young and vicious
We are the young and vicious!
snake eyes , they never lie
Snake eyes, they never lie,
fly high with pride
and leave your fears behind
지겨워 , 우리들의 광란의 party
Jigyeowo, urideurui gwangranui party,
보여줄게 환상 safari
Boyeojulge hwansang safari!
baddie , baddie , n0body can stop me
Baddie, baddie, nobody can stop me,
끼리끼리 붙어 , come on closer
Kkirikkiri buteo, come on closer!
go , go , \ub354 \ube68\ub9ac
Go, go, deo ppareuge!
act in \u2019 all naughty
Acting all naughty,
\uc2f9 \ub2e4 \ubd80\uc154 \ubaa8\uc870\ub9ac , \ubaa8\uc870\ub9ac \uc2f9\ub2e4 \ub2e4\ub2e4\ub2e4
Ssak da busyeo mojori, mojori ssak da dadada!
shake it off , what goes around
Shake it off, what goes around,
shut your mouth , will come back down
Shut your mouth, will come back down!
ready the fight , ready the screaming
Ready the fight, ready the screaming,
abracadabra , let \u2019s go
Abracadabra, let's go!
watch it , we reap in \u2019 it all ( reap in \u2019 it all )
Watch it, we reap in it all!
준비 ~ !
Ready~!
that ’s good game , what a shame .
that's good game, what a shame.
players , they all complain
players, they all complain,
" why me ? " " no not again ! "
"Why me?" "No, not again!"
shout ! ratatata ~ but !
Shout! Ratatata~ but!
ain't got time so dry those eyes
look around what ’s that i spy
Look around, what's that I spy?
the broken and bruised all got something to prove now
abracadabra let ’s go
Abracadabra, let's go!
watch them like dice as they fall
끝까지 가보자 go
Go all the way, go!
나는 내 맘 대로 해, hey
I do things my own way, hey!
double one , double win
Double one, double win,
lowly to lottery
do or die
we hit that high
snake eyes , snake eyes
Snake eyes, snake eyes,
come on now don ’t be shy
Come on now, don't be shy.
snake eyes , snake eyes
Snake eyes, snake eyes,
뜨겁게 달아올라
Burning up hot,
놀아 all day all night
Play all day, all night,
so turn it up can ’t stop won ’t stop preachin
So turn it up, can't stop, won't stop preachin',
who said the sky ’s the limit ?
Who said the sky's the limit?
show them that we mean business
we are the young and vicious
snake eyes they never lie
fly high with pride and leave your fears behind
지겨워 !
I'm sick of it!
우리들의 광란의 party
Our frantic party,
보여줄게 환상 safari
I'll show you a fantasy safari,
baddie baddie , nobody can stop me
Baddie baddie, nobody can stop me,
끼리끼리 붙어 , come on closer !
Flock together, come on closer!
go ! go ! 더 빨리
Go! Go! Faster,
check it out
actin all naughty
싹 다 부숴 모조리 모조리 싹 다 다다다 !
Smash everything completely, smash it all up!
shake it off , what goes around
Shake it off, what goes around,
shut your mouth , will come back down
Shut your mouth, will come back down,
ready the fight , ready the screaming
Ready the fight, ready the screaming,
abracadabra let ’s go
Abracadabra, let's go!
watch it we reap in it all
끊이지 않는 의지
Unending determination,
될대로 돼 볼래 play
Play, come what may,
reason , our demon
Reason, our demon,
believe in the beaten
just wait and see
we hit that high
snake eyes , snake eyes
Snake eyes, snake eyes,
come on now don ’t be shy
Come on now, don't be shy.
snake eyes , snake eyes
Snake eyes, snake eyes,
뜨겁게 달아올라
Burning up hot,
놀아 all day all night
Play all day, all night,
let the beat drop !
Let the beat drop!
go ! we go hard
Go! We go hard,
기사회생 전부를 걸어 bet
Revive and bet it all,
go ! we go hard i want it all
Go! We go hard, I want it all,
다시 일어나 파괴와 재생
Rise again, destruction and rebirth,
죽지 않아 , 전부 걸어
I won't die, I'm betting it all,
맞서 싸워 , 시작이야
Fight back, this is the start,
take the crown
끝까지 달려가
Run all the way,
rule the game
we ’ll hit that high
We'll hit that high!
snake eyes , snake eyes
Snake eyes, snake eyes,
come on now don ’t be shy
Come on now, don't be shy.
snake eyes , snake eyes
Snake eyes, snake eyes,
같이 춤을 추어 봐 , 이렇게
Dance together like this,
멈출 수 없어 같이 dance all night
Can't stop, let's dance all night together,
준비 ~ !
Ready~!
don ’t be afraid of losing
Don't be afraid of losing,
it ’s just a new beginning
It's just a new beginning,
look at the cards we dealing
Look at the cards we're dealing,
sometimes it takes a villain
snake eyes the time is nigh
fly high with pride and leave all fears behind !
Fly high with pride and leave all fears behind!
It's finally out!
I hope you all enjoyed my new song Snake Eyes!
Snake eyes, snake eyes, snake eyes, snake eyes, snake eyes!
This has been such a long process in the making.
I mean the make -- I haven't even talked!
I'm exhausted, but also I'm so happy! It's finally out!
Uh, my newest song Snake Eyes was what I just performed.
Not only is it not the first time that I've written a lot of the lyrics from scratch,
but also it's the first time choreographing a multi-member song,
multi-member with the two back dancers.
I'm so happy! I did it!
Uh, I hope you guys enjoyed it. Now, very important, pay attention.
The MV of this new song is also going to be premiering very soon after the live is over,
and it is going to be my first-ever 3D music video!
Oh, I'm so excited. 新曲がちょっとね...
Oh, I'm so excited. The new song is a bit, you know...
めちゃくちゃ嬉しいです。
I'm super happy!
ええと、このあとライブの後ね、初の3D MVもプレミアするので、あの、見てください！お願いします！
Um, after the live, um, my first 3D MV will premiere, so please watch it, I beg of you!
歌詞、えーの英語の歌詞はほぼ、あの、自分で書いたので、
The English lyrics, I mostly wrote them myself,
あの、あと韓国語もね、あの、頑張っててたんで、あの、聴いてください！
and I also worked hard on the Korean parts, so please listen to it!
streaming also begin shortly as well. it should be local local time -- I I never know anything, but it'll happen soon.
The streaming should also begin shortly as well. It should be local time -- I never know anything, but it'll happen soon.
So please make sure to check it out afterwards!
Oh, I hope I did okay. I was stressed about the choreography for a very long time, but...
Now, it's time! It's the thing you've all been waiting for: a merch showcase!
グッズを紹介に行きたいと思います！これは今回のラインナップでございます！
Let's introduce the birthday merch that you've all been waiting for! This is the lineup for this time!
Hakos Baelz 2026 Birthday merch -- what does the full set look like?
Here is what the full set looks like, and then we can go through them one by one.
What do we have first? First up, 最初は...何でしょう？
What do we have first? First up, what is it?
We have the [RECOLOR] Rubber Mat! Look at that beauty. This illustration is of course by my beloved mama, Mika Pikazo sensei.
今年もうね、描いてくださってありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for drawing it again this year!
Um, I just thought, you know, my very first birthday merch was also actually had like a rubber mat in it. And since, you know, I have a new outfit, I thought it was only fitting that, you know, we have another rubber mat um for me to switch out. I I really want this, so that's why I made -- as I wanted it. And you know you can use it for...
Um, I just thought, you know, my very first birthday merch also actually had like a rubber mat in it, and since, you know, I have a new outfit, I thought it was only fitting that, you know, we have another rubber mat for me to switch out. I really want this, so that's why I made it as I wanted it. And, you know, you can use it for...
Oh, o- also look at this! This!
Oh, also look at this! This!
And it is just really pretty, look at it.
And it's really pretty, look at it.
Ah. Look at it, it's so pretty.
Thank you so much. I know. Mamama, kotoshi mo ne,
Thank you so much. I know. Mamama, this year too,
Mika-mama ni, ano, irasuto kaite kudasattan de, hajimasu.
Mika-mama drew the illustration for us, so let's start.
Arigatou gozaimasu! Zehi zehi katte kudasai!
Thank you very much! Please definitely buy it!
And, well, what's the next item? Second is...
Ta-da! The recolor plushie keychain designed after my new outfit!
I've always wanted like a- a mini, you know, um, plushie that- that I can come out with. Um, you know, I have some, but I think it was just- it was just really fitting 'cause I have a new outfit.
I've always wanted a mini plushie that I can take out with me. I have some, but I think it's really fitting because I have a new outfit,
And I wanted a plushie in the new outfit. I can take her around places, you know, and- and you can photograph her, chukka, I don't know, take pat her, I don't know. Whatever you want to do.
and I wanted a plushie in the new outfit. I can take her around places, you know, photograph her, chukka, I don't know, pat her, I don't know, whatever you want to do.
But it's a plushie keychain, so it comes with a ball chain so you can attach it to your bag!
You see? She's so cute! Look at those squishy cheeks! Macchakai, issho, ki,
You see? She's so cute! Look at those squishy cheeks! Super cute, together, key, um,
ano, nuigurumi ki hōruda nan de, nanka kaban ni tsuketari toka ne, dekiru no de, meccha kichai kawaii kanji ni narimashita. Arigatou gozaimasu!
um, it's a plushie keyholder, so you can attach it to your bag, and it turned out super cute and tiny. Thank you very much!
Ee- to, tsugi! What is the next one?
Um, next! What is the next one?
Kore desu! The lil plushie shed pouch! It is a pouch.
This is it! The lil plushie shed pouch! It is a pouch.
It is a- a pouch for the plushie if you get both. It's like a set, you know?
It's a pouch for the plushie if you get both, like a set, you know?
Because, you know, you want to take your little bae out into the world, but what if- what if she gets dirty, you know, or like, you know, you don't want her to get to- if she gets snagged on a corner, she rips. You got to protect your little bae.
Because you want to take your little bae out into the world, but what if she gets dirty, you know? Or you don't want her to get—if she gets snagged on a corner and rips, you gotta protect your little bae,
So you have a lil plushie shed to house your little bae! Um, but it fits perfectly and, you know, you can use it. The design is also really cool as well.
so you have a lil plushie shed to house your little bae! But it fits perfectly and, you know, you can use it. The design is also really cool as well.
Um, next, last but not least, is something very special. It is a voice pack, but it is my first ever ASMR voice pack.
Next, last but not least, is something very special. It is a voice pack, but it is my first ever ASMR voice pack.
Um, I- I get really embarrassed doing ASMR stuff, but I just saw, you know, since it's a special occasion, maybe it'd be nice to have my very first ASMR voice pack. It- it features an intimate scene
I get really embarrassed doing ASMR stuff, but I just thought, you know, since it's a special occasion, maybe it'd be nice to have my very first ASMR voice pack. It features an intimate scene
with you guys after the live show! So if you want to, you know, check it out, please do. Eh, boku hatsu- hatsu- hatsuno ASMR boisu senario boisu nande, moshi kini- kinitteru kata wa zehi kiite kudasai!
with you guys after the live show! So if you want to check it out, please do. It's my very first ASMR scenario voice, so if anyone's interested, please be sure to listen to it!
Arigatou gozaimasu! It's called "Forever Your Bae." Hazukashii!
Thank you very much! It's called "Forever Your Bae." So embarrassing!
Anyway, here are the full set purchase bonuses! Ta-da-da-da-dan! The postcard!
You get a limited edition which- the limited edition, sorry, features a handsigned autograph and also a handwritten message from yours truly, just to- extra way to say thank you very much.
You get a limited edition—the limited edition, sorry, features a hand-signed autograph and also a handwritten message from yours truly, just an extra way to say thank you very much.
Um, and the standard version comes with the foil-stamped duplicate uh autograph and message.
And the standard version comes with the foil-stamped duplicate autograph and message.
I'm about to- about to die, but it's all right.
I'm about to—about to die, but it's all right.
Uh, thank you so much! Eh, toku- toku- tokuchou- yabai yome! Kaji- kanji ga nandakke? Ano, toku- tokutei wa kochira desu! Arigatou gozaimasu. Posukado...
Thank you so much! Um, special—special features—oh gosh, what was the kanji again? Um, the specifics are right here! Thank you very much. Postcard...
eh, to... hikki- hikki- hikikijitsusai- to messēji ga arimasu. Arigatou gozaimasu!
um, with... hand- handwritten message included. Thank you very much!
Oh my god, my brain is just—it's gone. I'm so tired. But anyway,
um, I think that's it. Oh wait, no, there's also a bonus voice! Wait, I forgot. Um, so with the full set, there is a bonus voice pack that is also ASMR that's on top of the already ASMR voice pack. Just a- little extra thing to say thank you. Um, that's it. I'm embarrassed. Anyway, yes.
I think that's it. Oh wait, no, there's also a bonus voice! Wait, I forgot. With the full set, there is a bonus voice pack that is also ASMR on top of the already ASMR voice pack, just a little extra thing to say thank you. That's it. I'm embarrassed. Anyway, yes.
So buy like this! Arigatou gozaimasu! Hai!
So buy like this! Thank you very much! Yes!
Before we continue, I guess, um, there is a little bit after, so I'm going to go put my jacket on real quick, if that's okay. I'll be right back. Chotto, hikaete kimasu.
Before we continue, I guess, um, there's a little bit after, so I'm going to go put my jacket on real quick, if that's okay. I'll be right back. I'll step backstage for a moment.
Ta-da! Mada dekimasu. Hai! Raima desu. Eh, to, just putting my jacket...
Ta-da! I'm back. Yes! Right now, just put on my jacket.
I'm so happy that, you know, I got to do another birthday live this year, even though it's not really my birthday. Um, I'm so happy
I'm so happy that, you know, I got to do another birthday live this year, even though it's not really my birthday. I'm so happy
that I got to show my new outfit. I'm just happy that I got a new outfit. It's so easy to dance in. I love the way it looks.
that I got to show my new outfit. I'm just happy that I got a new outfit. It's so easy to dance in, and I love the way it looks.
And today I got to dance with so many, uh, of my friends. It was so much fun. I got to challenge myself.
And today I got to dance with so many of my friends. It was so much fun. I got to challenge myself.
It's always an amazing, amazing experience being able to do a birthday live, yeah, kyou ne,
It's always an amazing, amazing experience being able to do a birthday live. Yeah, today,
ano, ippai no memba to issho ni odotte, mecchaku ureshikute, moshisanshou mo meccha ureshi- ureshikute, mou tonikaku ureshii desu.
um, dancing with so many members was super happy, and the 3rd fes was also super hap—happy, and I'm just so happy.
Ano, minna mo ne... a lot of planning that goes into these, um, all the staff and everyone, stuff sanyou ne, minna mo ne...
Um, everyone too... a lot of planning that goes into these, all the staff and everyone, everyone too...
Everyone's...
力
str-
あの
Um...
が必要 もうなんだかもう英語か日本語かもうわかんないす すいません はい
I need... I don't know, I can't tell if I'm speaking English or Japanese. Sorry!
I just mixed up my languages, but
Please do check out the new song MV that's coming out shortly. I'm really, really proud of it.
Um, but that's kind of it. That's all I have for today.
But, there is a final encore song that I wanted to sing, that I think really sums up today's live.
So, if if you would like to stay- please stay to the end. Please listen. Please don't go anywhere.
So, if you'd like to stay—please stay to the end. Please listen. Please don't go anywhere.
ちょっとかなと最後の1曲あります。今日のテーマにぴったりの曲だと思うので、最後まで聴いてください。
So I have one final song. I think it fits today's theme perfectly, so please listen to the very end.
はい
Yes!
あとMV、あ、の新曲のMVも見てくださいね。はい、あ、じゃ、最後の曲、最後の曲、どうぞ。
Also check out the MV for the new song! Okay, alright, then for the final song... go ahead.
魂の色は 何色ですか
What color is your soul?
「もういいっさ 折れたままで」
"It's okay if it stays broken,"
捨てるほど 逃げ出すほど 強くないよ
not strong enough to throw away or run from it.
ほら もう一度 鼓動高鳴る
Look, my heartbeat echoes once again.
何が正しくかなんて わからないけど
I don't know what's right or wrong, but
形のないものばかりが 大切になっていく
only things without form are becoming precious.
飾らない言葉だけが 強く結ばれてる
Only unadorned words are tightly bound together.
また躓いて 転がって それでも砕けない
Stumbling and rolling again, yet still unbreakable.
魂の色は 何色ですか
What color is your soul?
ただ傷ついて 強がって それでも見つけたいよ
Just getting hurt, putting on a brave face, yet I still want to find it.
魂のカタチ 確かめてるよ
I'm confirming the shape of my soul.
深い地の底で 一人 扉と鍵を探す
Alone at the bottom of the deep earth, searching for a door and a key.
おとぎ話は ほら 泡の様に全部消えて
Look, fairy tales vanish completely like bubbles,
葛藤 残像だけ 次のページへ
leaving only conflicts and afterimages for the next page.
伸びてく枝葉が 分かれて それぞれの道を行く
Growing branches and leaves split, each going its own way.
寂しい想いだけが 強く根を張ってる
Only lonely memories have deep, strong roots.
また貫いて 失って それでも挫けない
Piercing through and losing again, yet still unbroken.
心はどこに 器はどこに
Where is the heart? Where is the vessel?
ただ残されて 抜け落ちて それでも伝えたいよ
Just left behind, slipping away, yet I still want to convey it.
魂の日々の 魂の志を
The days of the soul, the will of the soul,
ずっと ずっと
forever and ever...
魂の色は
What color...
何色ですか
...is your soul?
赤い色ですか
Is it red?
青い色ですか
Is it blue?
魂の色は 何色ですか 何色ですか 何色ですか
What color is your soul? What color is it? What color is it?
透明な過去に 不透明な明日に 生きるあなたは 何色ですか
In a transparent past, in an opaque tomorrow, what color are you living in?
また躓いて 転がって それでも砕けない
Stumbling and rolling again, yet still unbreakable.
魂の色は 何色ですか
What color is your soul?
ただ傷ついて 強がって それでも見つけたいよ
Just getting hurt, putting on a brave face, yet I still want to find it.
魂のカタチ 確かめてるよ
I'm confirming the shape of my soul.
確かめるように ずっと
Always making sure...
ずっと
Always...
NEW 3D OUTFIT?!
Hakos Baelz Birthday Live 2026